Emmanuel Uchenna

Experienced Frontend Developer



eunithelp@gmail.com ==

(+234) (0) 811-0863-115

Ebonyi, Nigeria 🖊

https://eunit99.github.io 🗞

https://github.com/eunit99

https://linkedin.com/in/eunit99 in

CAREER PROFILE

Passionate frontend developer with 4+ years developing responsive, intuitive frontend solutions. I am looking to obtain a frontend developer role where my responsive UI design skills, my knowledge in a wide variety of software, programming languages will contribute to building high performing, accessible and scalable web applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

frontend developer

Credipple

Nov. 2020 - Jan. 2021 Remote

Accomplishments / Tasks

- Converted UI mockups to functional, responsive website using HTML, CSS, JavaScript/JQuery.
- Worked with a team to build the home and about pages
- Charged with the responsibility of developing responsive user interfaces.

frontend developer

LabsAl

Mar. 2020 - May 2020

Remote

Accomplishments / Tasks

- Built responsive conversational user interfaces for chatbots
- Successfully developed the landing page of Edubots

Chatbot developer

LabsAl

Mar. 2019 - Sep. 2020

Remote

Accomplishments / Tasks

- Built various enterprise chatbots ranging from psychological, educational chatbots. These include:
- hapBot: A bot to supply happiness tips
- Ella bot: A bot to teach basic English grammar
- **Bo**: A chatbots to make high schools inclusive and welcoming as possible.

INDUSTRY EXPERTISE

Single Page App Development Storybook

Responsive Web Development Accessibility

GIT / Version Control Component Design

Web Scrapping User Interface Design

SKILLS

HTML5 CSS3 JavaScript ReactJS

jQuery SASS/SCSS Styled Components

CERTIFICATIONS

Frontend development (2020 - 2021) Udemy.com

EDUCATION

Bsc. Anatomy (in view)

Alex Ekwueme Federal University, Ebonyi State

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

French

Bilingual Proficiency

Igbo

Native or Bilingual Proficiency